Is that the King of England skulking about?
英格兰国王在躲什么吗
Fancy some?
想要一些吗
This was reserved for the Prime Minister,but
这是预留给首相的  但是
that fat bastard does not need any more pie.
那个胖杂种不再需要派了
I could always sell paseries.
我可以一直卖小点心
You know, if you decide to disband the Monarchy
你知道的 如果你决定要解散君主制
which I am all for, by the way.
顺便说一下 我很赞成
Something tells me your opinion is in the minority.
我有预感 像你一样赞成的人占少数
And when has that mattered?
这重要吗
You trust your instincts. You follow your heart.
你相信你的直觉   跟随着你的心
That's what makes you great.
这成就了你的伟大
A great king.
一个伟大的国王
And a kind of okay father.
和一个还凑合的父亲
How are you, Lenny?
你好吗 莱尼
Um...
嗯
I'm sad.
我很伤心
But I'm baked out of my mind...
但我已经不想这些了
So right now I'm well.
所以现在我还好
They worry about you.
他们很担心你
Your mother, Liam.
你的妈妈 利亚姆
Not you?
而不是你
Not so much.
我不是很担心你
Oh, thanks a lot!
哦 真是太感谢了